/semen /say In some cultures, semen is attributed with special properties of masculinity. For instance, among the Etoro people of Papua New Guinea, it is believed that young boys must fellate their elders and ingest their sperm to achieve proper sexual maturation. 

/redneck /say <moparisthebest> Im proud of being a redneck :)

/silab /say <MissSilabSoft> so stork i figured out that i get about 8000 different people a night :p

/poem {
  say There once was a girl from Heath
  say She liked to peel back foreskin with her teeth
  say It wasn't for money or anything funny
  say but to get to the cheese underneath
}

/42 {
  say A programming genius called Hugh
  say Said 'I really must see if it's true.'
  say So he wrote a routine
  say To ask 'What's it all mean?'
  say But the answer was still '42'.
}

/mopman /say <Mopman> a mopar linux distro would crash every 5 minutes | say <Mopman> but it would have an auto restarter

/stork /say <stork> on a good day, my ego blocks out the sun

/cream /say <Mopman> i got a mouthful of cream

/asians {
  say <Bob_Lablah> I wonder how moparisdongs gets the results from google:(
  say <frunk> it employs asians
}

/jmecar /say <jme_009> I dunno, we did it in a car

/jmedoor /say <jme_009> I did the bathroom door handle(the inside)

/emo /say <jme_009> Why did Pwnd get kicked out of Disney Land? He was cutting in line

/rictoo /say <Rictoo> I WANT CUM | say <Rictoo> My sexuality is gay

/dump /say <newbiehacker> I did a complete font dump once | say <Aftermath> I took a dump once

/pd /say <pd> freenode is fine | say <pd> everyone shush | say * pd was kicked by SilabBot (Stop Spamming!)

/cut {
  say <pwnd_> I try cut self
  say <pwnd_> but fail
}

/dog /say <jme_009> i come into the living rom, bend over to pet my dog | say <jme_009> fucking spill my milk all over :P

/cock /say <Thug-life> 195 bottles of cock to go

/capslock {
  say <Sensored3> YAY THE CAPSLOCK KICK IS GONE
  say * Sensored3 was kicked by Nintendo (Turn caps lock OFF!)
}

/oct /say Why do programmers always get Christmas and Halloween mixed up? | say Because DEC 25 = OCT 31

/pregg /say <pregg> dang it, its 9:58, 2 minutes till bed time =.

/taharok {
  /say <Taharok> MissSilabSoft but the power of the government was granted by God
  /say <Taharok> MissSilabSoft there is not a single flaw in the Bible
}

/mopeat /say <Mopman> but then my dad decided to give me more than i could actually eat

/pills /say <jme_009> Yeah, don't take this the wrong way, but Im good at swallowing large stuff

/maps /say I personally believe that US Americans are unable to do so because some people out there in our nation don't have maps and I believe that our education like such as in South Africa and The Iraq everywhere like such as and I believe that they should our education over here in the US should help the US or 
should help South Africa and should help The Iraq and the Asian countries so we will be able to build up our future for our children.

/milkshake /say My whipped ice dairy drink brings the attention of many males to my place of residence and/or employment, and they declare that its quality far surpasses that of yours. Absolutely, it far surpasses yours. I could convey to you the recipe, but i would have to demand compensation.

/offtopic /say $1 $+ : $2- is off-topic on freenode. Please view the rules at http://freenode.net/policy.shtml

/women /say <moparisthebest> the women I prefer weigh around 200 :P

/halp /say http://[u][i][b]can any one help ne plzzz i need halp bad!!!!!!!!!! ???[/b][/i][/u]

/littlekid /say <rough_rider_hyperrobbie> im done arguing with you little kid

/quux /say <quux> 8 hours ago, a staffer was kickbanned from this place and made fun of, repeatedly.

/jmegirl /say <jme_009> ever since i wuz a little girl, i've always wanted a cock in my ass

/jmelunix /say <jme_009> while scanning the lunix server(which runescape is ran on), I came across a java hack that confuses the kernal.

/feces /say my mummy and daddy handed me feces on a plate when i was little | say they told me to eat it and play with myself

/stomped /say <Jake_AKA_Pimping_One> dude stop trying to act tough over the internet we all know you get your ass stomped alot..

/headon /say <KM93> i just had a wank, and my bro is coming up the stairs, wut i do with ma cum! | say <Sensored3> KM93 APPLY DIRECTLY TO THE FOREHEAD

/batch /say wow... im a java coder, and i make batch files all the time... and im too dumb to make one? i wrote a folder locking hack for batch, and im still too dumb to make one?

/coding /say I have not said it is a coding you f dumb noob .. SO SHUT UP NOOB!. I made the tut.. and I posted in this section.. well idc.. I HAVE NOT SAID IT IS A FUCKING CODING

/aussieboys /say Hi, we are 2 boys from Australia and we can't both get on moparscape... why cant we both play? My bro can always get in but I can't. It downloads on my laptopo to 17% then closes. We want to be able to play at the same time like we do on runescape...

/vb /say <vbcoderx> hmm.. in java u use a batch file to compile and run code..

/xpkx /say <x-pk-x> faggot ass computer nerd gunna try an talk shit over the comp

taste {
  say <amcsi> young girls and cocks
  say <amcsi> interesting taste
  say <c|p> yes they do have an interesting taste
}

/religion /say Ok if you think religion is a waste of time, have fun in hell..

/iq {
  say <dftpnkezln> For all of you reporting a score more than 100 as you iq lol @ you. How can you possibly score more than 100%?
  say <dftpnkezln> I'm very happy with my score of 89.
}

/jdk /say <Lusfr|AFK> Does enyone have Jagex Development Kit (Jdk) 5 or 6, so i can compile, computer got reformatted so i need 2 get it so i can compile.

/trace /say rofl you dumb ass white boy dork gtfo you dumb ass b4 i trace your ip and beat your ass

/fbi {
  say * Your IP address has been logged by the Child Internet Service Protection Agency. Please wait while memory ref code "XXXXX5151" is entered into the database.
  say NOTICE TO USER: The Federal Bureau of Investigation has logged a record of files downloaded along with the IP addresses of the users participating in downloading to these files due to potential violations of U.S. law. If you think this info was logged in error, please call your local F.B.I. office and quote the reference number #2334531343. VIOLATION: Possession of child pornography.
}

/seizure /say During the episode when Ash and co. are with Porygon in Cyber Space, missiles get fired at them from Team Rocket. Pikachu blasts the missiles with Thunderbolt causing a flashing of red and blue which put 800 Japanese children into hospital with epileptic seizures. After this the show was put on a 4 month hiatus and was almost totally banned with Nintendo to be blamed for it

/beers /say i drank like ffour beers and now i have a fucking handover

/bribe {
  say <Thug-life> i can talk in bribe on irc !!
  say <Thug-life> ... . ... ..   .......... . .. .. . .. .
}

/noises /say I have a baby sister that's 3 years old and is sick and she sleeps in my bedroom and when u crash my computer moniter makes noices atleast every minute and she wakes up and she cry's... not very nice?

/dont /say nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo dont dont dont dont dont take drugs =[ its bad for health please dont...

/dontx /say nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo dont dont dont dont dont $$1- =[ its bad for health please dont...

/croc /say Two crocodiles were flying. One was green, the other was going to Africa, too. The first one asks, "How much does a pound of fried nails cost?" The second one replies, "What shoes? I graduated long ago"

/xbox {
  /say Why do they call it the $$2- $$1 $+ ?
  /say Because when you see it, you will turn $$1 degrees and walk away.
}

/offence /say NO OFFENCE BUT fuck u......... u idiot ur family idiot.. mother fucker why dont he fucking lock the topic if he dont want people to thank him.....what else people want to say???? + why he sticked this shit

/rage /say http://img530.imageshack.us/img530/5613/motivator491132bh8.jpg

bigdog /say http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VXJZVZFRFJc

gf {
  say Thug-life :  Guys i have a girlfriend now ! :)
  say Thug-life :  i gave her 30k on runescape
  say Thug-life :  and she is now my girlfriend!!
}

/vista /say lol this faget is jealos i got vista what does he have windows 96 rofl lmao Tongue Cool winksmile shifty and btw i woudlnt take that from a junior lol Tongue

/jealous /say lol this faget is jealos i got $$1 what does he have $$2- rofl lmao Tongue Cool winksmile shifty and btw i woudlnt take that from a junior lol Tongue

/dawg /say hell no dawg! i hate weed that kills u man ita babad 4 u stop guys i wanna see u guys another day ur gonna kill ursevles smoking this weed and cigg1es!!!!

/prostate /say What happened is that I touched my prostate, and then I started pumping cum.

/coder /say Atleast i post threads instead of pretending im a coder, if your such great coder lets have a coding competition??

/nerd /say shut the hell up i aint a no lifer nerd like u...

/shitmom say One day i was taken a shit and my mom came in told me to get up. Then she ate my crap!!!

/babby /say They need to do way instain mother> who kill thier babbys. becuse these babby cant frigth back it was on the news this mroing a mother in ar who had kill her three kids . they are taking the three babby back to new york too lady to rest my pary are with the father who lost his chrilden ; i am truley sorry for your lots

/has /say has anyone really been far as decided to use even go want to do look more like?

/gangsta /say u think ur not gangsta i fucking own u dick head u no ur a fucking noob u shithead u cant fucking do anything u nerd u online u dickhead thats right i went the u ass hole i wood own u bubba wood own u bubba more gangsta the u will ever be nigger stupid  shthead

/ambition /say Ambition is like a frog sitting on a Venus's-flytrap. The flytrap can bite and bite, but it won't bother the frog because it only has little tiny plant teeth. But some other stuff could happen and it could be like ambition.

/tank /say Two fish are sitting in a tank. One turns to the other and says "hey, do you know how to drive this thing?"

/naver /say wtf did i do $$1- i naver did sht to u thats right ur just a fucking noob looking for fight u faggot i wood smash u so fucking much u wood be dead u fat fucking ass hole get off the fucking computer and get a fucking life why dont ya

/chest /say I found this highly pleasurable and shot loads all over my chest!

/shit /say Yeah well you're shit and you're worth shit now get the fuck off my topic. Reported fucker. Get the fuck off you're worth nothing here...

/11 /say I fucking own dude...You people dont expct much from a 11 year old, but your all soon to be fucked up XD

/efficiency /say Everything will be stored in a Database. Note that this might not be as fast as a local file, but it is more efficient. And I personally value efficiency over speed.

/fetus /say http://img329.imageshack.us/img329/1408/loolrw9.jpg

/evelation {
  say what do u belive in evelation or creation?
  say i say creation!!
  say eveltion says we were monkeys ow thats stupid
}

/private {
  say A man and a woman are attending a computer science lecture. After the teacher leaves the man touches the woman's boobs.
  say "Hey! That's private!" said the woman.
  say The man responds "But I thought we were in the same class!".
}

/empty {
  say A physicist, a biologist and a mathematician are sitting in a street café watching people entering and leaving the house on the other side of the street. First they see two people entering the house. Time passes. After a while they notice three people leaving the house. The physicist says, "The measurement wasn't accurate." The biologist says, "They must have reproduced." The mathematician says, "If one more person enters the house then it will be empty."
}

/stone /say if someone were to smash a stone with a sledgehammer, would you consider that murder?

/door /say Imagine punching somebody so hard that they turned into a door. Then, you find out that's where all doors come from, and you were initiated into a murder club that makes doors. The stronger you punch, the better the door. So, there are super strong murders who punch people into Venetian doors and shit.

/athletic /say if you know your more of a no lifer than me im new to alot of this shit you fucjking gay cock sucking bitch so stfu and go get laid maybe youll have a better attitude cuz if u were even the slightest bit athletic u wouldnt be on here.............

/athletic2 /say if u were even the slightest bit athletic u wouldnt be on here.............

/regex /say Some people, when confronted with a problem, think "I know, I'll use regular expressions." Now they have two problems.

rasmus /say I'm not a real programmer. I throw together things until it works then I move on. The real programmers will say "Yeah it works but you're leaking memory everywhere. Perhaps we should fix that." I’ll just restart Apache every 10 requests.

/cauliflower {
  say <moparisthebest_> once I accidentally ate an entire head of cauliflower that way
  say <moparisthebest_> BOY did I regret that later!!!!
}

/ha /say HAHAHAHAHAHAHAH

/heron  /say i am a heron. i haev a long neck and i pick fish out of the water w/ my beak. if you dont repost this comment on 10 other pages i will fly into your kitchen tonight and make a mess of your﻿ pots and pans

/lobster /say i am a rock lobster. i eat rocks. my favourite song is 'love shack' by the b-52s. i hate their other song, rock lobster, as i feel it doesn't truly capture the spirit of what i represent

/heroncarpet
/say @stork | imagine having a carpet made of live herons
/say @stork | then you'd be fucking confused
/say @stork | they'd be like squaking and pecking ahd shit
/say @stork | and you'd be like stop pecking me you're a carpet
/say @stork | but they'd be like *peck peck peck*

/intelligence /say  why are you insulting my intelligence, you're some inbred working for free on some autistic project dont talk down on me retard, i study hard and work hard, what do you do with your life, im ranked 5 out of the 310 math students and 1/x for cs, what do you do, tell me your accolades, or you wanna keep talking you autistic shitbag


